Red were rare
rare. Rare rare
rather
rapid
. Yes. ERIN
BURNETT. Ready.
M.L.
Rural.
Rather.
Err
I.
Think. So that's why thank you.
Gee that shows the talk of the. Well we've
got to get back to the hotel and get out
things paid for somehow Chiles the twelve
o'clock to night funny it does with you
me. I've decided to stay In fact
if I plan to work out right I may
never. Forgot to go back we lose our job
at the fish market in Des Moines Well
that's why there's plenty
of fish. Here in Paris.
Just another glass of
milk and two fresh from.
You know what I think you are
hiding something from me. If.
The the.
Round. Pen is truly informed
I'll send you just.
The day of your past.
Twenty You can just remember. I mean the
timing if you're in general I think really
he needs to have
a time. The
the. Yes man. The fantasy is
that you're welcome for the
use of flowers just that it was just
a phone and if yes just chucked it but I
thought maybe you might want something to
nibble on while you were
swelling the flour.
Where do you. Damages you keep
the secret show us I'm in love
you don't tell me who it is now most
God just preacher in the. Joint yet
the N.T. Puts God Well I
don't blame you she sure is
a swell day she says me yes sir
don't call her a day she's
a girl and I'm going to marry
going alone this time and right.
Boy it sure is allowed Yes. Say we're going
to get married just as soon as I ask
then why don't you ask and now that we
can all go out and celebrate that's just
what I intended it you will get cleaned
up and I'll go down and ask the question
that check when I tell you show me that
a lot and I'm now going to
measure my When are you going.
What are you doing with that
cushion. I keep on but it may have.
Very. In front of the window
where you can stand up.
Yes. How
anyone could be so stupid as to stand
there and contend yes is beyond me.
You.
Oh why don't you stand in the
window thanks to my new Spanish.
Oh. Yes I'm sorry. If this
thing didn't think he's funny
is this for me yes but remember George S.
You are mad at women and friends. Yes I
am just an American way of you
mind being. The get out of this.
Somehow some don't come.
So good to see you after this long time was
dismissed all you want to project when
issues. Songs.
Oh my darling shows up I've waited every
day every hour every minute. I worried
about you we are back and I'd love to love
the terribly lonely but that's all over
now I've got good news for you I made
arrangements for you to join me when I go
back. I'm so happy.
To hang on to funky. And I'm
great that's right it was
just put me in the mood. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Throw it over your shoulder.
Thanks so.
Thank you have your prayer.
My friend and I like
a bottle of wine and drink treat that. We
thought maybe you'd like to challenge.
You know I do expect you to use
a chair but if you still get that questionnaire
when I'm you know Stanek this will
be the first time I've ever
been married. The. Same as
having gone I told you God OK but the
matter you shared out of California
I know just how you feel let me fix it
for you I don't take shit just she. Said
he's got something to tell you something
to tell me yes he's not so bad here let's
just claim that. Congress. No I
don't mean that I mean he's crazy about
you he's going to matter here I'm jolly
cardstock company. You haven't
met me but that is if you don't
mind. He makes penalty so he's
not kidding he's on the left of
Charlie why thankfully. I was
never my sincerity in my life.
Then nitrogen I'm sure the community
will want to give me one chance to
challenge
a car ride out sure it's just
someone else. One day. Well
that's that. No use crying over
split. The body guard come on
or you. Remember Are You
Going out with me. I wanna
be. As.
You.
Can be young guy every minute
because you back and we.
Don't worry about it you'll
get over it all right.
I think this will happen to me just
a bit I'm in my life when I need
something real. Something else.
Some day. And. Why don't just try
a nice juicy steak or make it feel
better if yes believe me though I'm.
Getting some semblance of.
A rapper.
That. You.
Just did you.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Put some water on my head.
Yes. Yes yes.
Now is that that. May get wet.
Get.
You. Renting
a house like you do for us yes they
me own home. Don't talk to me like
that after all the hospital I've given
you have tried to give you a candy
a nice fat juicy steak I've waited on you
with yes face that tell you this plenty
of our girls you don't have to worry about
that at all. If I suspect that you are
gone drown myself. Then the you've
given me an idea what I'm going
to follow your advice good
and I drown myself oh wait
a minute now let's not I was only kidding
this is not time for Kitty I know but
don't you think your to think you don't but
at the end of in town I have thought it
over and says George it has given me the
air I have nothing left to live for oh
don't be silly Don't be silly this is
a fast better thing I do now
than I have ever done before.
Well compiling advice could lack what is
going. Well I don't want to get my name
dragged into this.
But. My first thought now when I count
three we'll both jump in. But if I'm going
to jump in there for I'm not in
the last so much that kind of
a guy you are after all I've done for you
let me jump in my own do you realize that
after I'm gone that you just go on living
by yourself people would care actually
and wonder what you are and I wouldn't be
here to tell them to be no one to protect
just do you want that to happen
to you. I never thought of that
and I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings or
all that I didn't mean to be so despite
that showed me that bygones be bygones
this is going to be easier than you think
I moved to tell you.
I. Don't. I already.
Compiled
a good bystander. One. Too
. Like what I just saw the something
that's your member when she was telling me
that when we passed away we come back
on the set and some other form like
a bird or
a dog are also samples Oh you mean
reincarnation Yes yes that's it well now that
we're going to go out what would you like
to be when you come back though I never
given it much thought. I like horses.
I guess I'd like to come back as
a horse. But would you like to be when
you come back oh I'd rather come back as
myself I always got along so well with
me and you can come back as yourself and
come on and stop wasting my
time are you ready compiled by.
Women want. To always just brother Sam.
You think the water is deep enough
maybe you might bump your head. Just
a little never thought of that.
Yet you.
Termites.
Happen next and that morning.
You know. That you want to get
you around the country in one
hundred thirty one I already. Shat
one. To have one hundred
of them to the top if you
tell them I was going to jump
in the red but I commit such
a foolish action on your travel companies
that was that when I went out and try the
tariff on the company's patent office of
the day I was next selling no woman as
well I should say enough you have to
proceed if you don't you risk I know I
understand but don't forget that
a plenty more efficiency is not
a problem with the patient it's
a girl that's just an expression my
friend I realize how you feel just
a few too much from there for sure you got
your job making life is too precious to
Pro way on account of those from woman
to probably as well they all do the
psychology what he'd want to be all right
but that was another man and I can't meet
him face to face but I am what the
No five is yet. Ralph the price
is cheap and if you listen to my suggestion
your problem is this off one issue or
six just joined up out of
Egypt. You want to talk to
a point there. That's not
a bad idea at all it's better than Chaplin
and you get equipped for getting all
that happens you're right Nancy thank
you that's just a talent there is
a pleasure going to. Have to get great this
next now we don't have to say we can't
join
a foreign legion and because I'll be back
in the mines on the seventeenth Well you're
right it was just time in the time that I
had missed that but if we turn up thank
you I'm going to take you to forget
no time at all just a matter of
a few days. When I shall write from the
free app and don't have to worry about it
says if I'm
a test run away. Thank. You
. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you. It's.
Been an adult.
I I'm on the path.
Yes. Very upset.
All right.
Second I'm. The first of the well.
Is pretty sure I don't but you pretty well
today that bill right now from New Day
As I look at this right.
Now. Yes.
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. Well of course they say oh no
that's well put me down. But I guess
last week I was just like yes and
nothing happened yet as you know this
show has never come of that this or that
somebody saying yes yes taken right out
he only looked that's going to have.
Heck I have done that. Then shot.
Back.
Good morning if I don't I'll sign you do
your duty revelry if I get dressed quickly
make up your bunks and get ready for
inspection and action until seven ten minutes
for breakfast you deliver one in
March and don't fall. What about.
That one marking to have inspections of six
fifteen minutes for mess kitchen duties
and don't turn inspection until eleven then
that. We have to do all that you won't
have time to think
a bunch of. How much do we get for
all this way one hundred sun to use
a day with national think. How much is
that in American money. American money.
Is a clear road to about three cents
a day of course it varies with the rate
of the city so how much do we get for
overtime there ain't going to be any all
but if you think the job and I get that
makes my God I me but three cents and
a friend you are crazy. So. Yeah
and that goes for me too course we don't
work for less than twenty five cents a K.
So we are.
Oh.
OK thanks.
OK.
Thanks.
X. . X.
.
X.
. X.
.
X. X. . X. X. . X.
. X. X. X. X. X. . X.
. X. . X. X. X. . X.
X. X.
. You.
Haven't I got an upcoming without to making
it come from well it's your own fault
if you and phone in love with George and
we wouldn't be here were never will you
stop reminding me of them here I am trying
to forget you keep coming about and all
the time now is another day wasted. Or
maybe don't try hard enough if you can
forget why don't you try and pretend to
forget Can anybody paid and doesn't get
well I know if it was me upset down and
relax I close my eyes not constant thanks
and think of nothing would be around then
that's what I had to say I think you've
done something I know
I've got some one to take
a whirl at it. Now I
don't think of anything I want.
I know it's tough to get
a swell gal like best
gorgeous harem lovely eyes.
Ears atrocities. Ruby lips. Goads.
I can see em now. So can I.
When you kept asking I concentrate when
you keep talking about all the time now
keep quiet let me alone now stand out.
Alex if you don't stop bothering me
I'm gonna punch you went on and I'll.
Tell you to quit then. Prove.
You're the best.
A lives when you get there without
washing the cook lunch at
a manicure then vegetables for them
as do I thank you past you heard.
Can you fix that how do you think we're
going to do all that remained I feel
something coming over
me to do. A miracle has
happened where I've come pretty clean
forgotten you mean you've forgotten Georgette
who's Georgette to you that's well now we
can finish the washing we can go home do
nothing we're going
now. Now you're talking
Absolutely. And I found them asleep
and when I told them to go back to
work that through return or in my fans.
True they did it very well show them what
it means and this is
a lie or others. I have. You
have to apply to get out of this garden
eight children if you got everything that I
was going to comment that tell them we are
throwing at the same time I give them
a piece of my mind I don't
blame you three cents
a day at that time. That.
Are not my God and my sump
pump under arrest Yes sir.
I want to take ideas he did not wait.
You know was what he is now ts of course
he's not here let's go look for it love
nothing I really don't know or I wouldn't
want to leave him out just leave him
a P S good enough for him.
Now he can put back this pipe and
smoke it maybe he doesn't smoke
a pipe or else whenever he hopes and well
you gotta be careful about those things.
What you like about Ali I said plenty and
if I can discover rasberry out of town on
a lark or That'll learn three
a day right. Never
during my Army career never mind how funny
I am covered here are we can I cut my
hand on.
A CUNT.
Amon has. Been listening. My
name. Is Telling new very Fruen onto my.
Tongue to stay on the dance.
Song long gone this moon
bullied my gal old.
MARY. Meredith Vieira.
MARY.
I wonder what time the playing the the
parents just don't know about that about me
I want the people just
around the corner you laugh.
That's all I want passed through that
gate no matter what happens just so.
Last. Night when I'm going to take
a plane always I should say not. I
wonder what. I don't know but I know
what keeps me down. Me too good to
repair a concept for me anyhow
a message for. Georgia
the only one you. Know I'm so happy and
that's why I'm here with you and you miss
me every day is going to.
Bring the cup for us.
Could you tell us the weight of
a road Depot. George A So you've
changed your mind darling I forgive you
and the piece I have talked to can you
forgot Don't be so how could I
forget my this is Joe agenda.
And.
Tomorrow. This is doomed.
What's the big idea the idea is that this
lady happens to be my wife who is that
still. Your wife yes you would be
home right just five centuries ago he
didn't understand is something to become
again I must speak the gentleman. No one
well I'm going to give you a piece of
advice keep away from my wife I have
a see your hear of you being and have
presence again I will see to it the goal
worthless can fly to fling in the desert
sun so you might feel about you want to
say yes. Yes.
A million times you don't have to worry
about that we are leaving right now we are
we. All. So.
Many fallen troops you get OUR know you
got your number when you signed it you're
signing your own water you're
under arrest for deception.
To keep
a close watch on yes sorry. To
do sorry. Come on out for your sweet.
Come. Wash me.
I'll see what sunrise I
will. Really get off.
From work to do what
you do you know where.
You're from. Case love. My job
keep your mouth shut.
The procedures of the phone
go in and we'll be shown
a strong voice. As
a nice place we are in.
Sunrise. Over crowded tomorrow.
Say oh wait while you still want to come
back I don't care if I'm never come back.
You.
I'll play another one
now. Half of our friends.
Find that eight hours. Pass.
This particular.
One Get me. An arm of the.
You. Know what is true.
Up. Is when are we going to Sterlings
to the house nice warm we're
making our escape. Route are we
allowed to do that. So I head.
Out into. The
business find the shell know where we
are still or is that flying the flag.
For the Jews.
To stand now we've got to dig our way out.
Go back to the cell and get those ten
plate number back to South when
you read this is our last chance.
To hire
a Polish two episodes. Always make. Me
. A captain. Never you you.
Bring the Panthers.
All right come on you're
the tongues out come up.
Oh. Come on.
It and I don't.
The prisoners have escaped. From
the cage and I know that time.
You want all for the planet and realize
all of the anti riposte the sheriff.
I wonder what time it is and I know I know.
I should be easy on the world right now
or. To Black to get work and I guess
you're right we better start digging up
a good idea. To.
Stop all this nonsense. Don't you dare go
back to bed together leave me alone see
you having. Oh bring
a bottle of that special
mint it was. Yes or.
It has.
To.
I wonder. If you somehow
don't have the force.
Have.
Yet.
Left America in.
The All right.
Oh.
You.
At
a time like this you have to do that.
Perhaps we get out of this. OK
. You.
Want to see the meaning of this. What do
we say if you take up your story I've got
my.
Air. If you happen to.
Have the best.
Basic essentials. And then I want to talk
before me was great for so long getting
so close to make
a bunch of diabetics whether brings them
back or beginning the last six weeks for
that's what.
Else.
We're all.
Yes bad.
RASH.
It is. Just.
A.
Measure. Has.
A lot. Of rubbish.
Yes. Sir I. Will want to.
Share.
Wow wow wow.
Read.
This.
I am.
Ever.
Watched you on.
A weekend of the slim
good let's get are you.
Test.
The earlier.
ERA or.
We're all
L.A.
.
Last.
Laugh.
Hello
hello. Hello
.
Well. Is.
A stand up I'm all right here.
Well here's another nice
mess you've gotten me into.
Really you can't really you
know of course it's the G.M.
Glad to see you. Yes.
Yes yes
yes. Yes
.